trefis.com 2012-12-04

# Privacy Policy -- Trefis

Date of Last Revision: February 19, 2012

Insight Guru, Inc. ("Insight Guru", "we", "us") provides its content and tools on its web site, Trefis, located at [http://www.trefis.com](http://www.trefis.com/) or as applications running on other partner sites (collectively referred to as the "Site"). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Site.

## 1\. Introduction

We are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, personal profile, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home.

If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the Site, we may transfer that Personal Information within the Site or to Insight Guru's third-party service providers, in order to provide services on the Site, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. We may also share your Personal Information with third-parties for any other use or uses to which you give your consent.

Insight Guru strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Insight Guru intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained. Finally, we may disclose your Personal Information if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or reasonably necessary to i) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, ii) enforce our Terms of Service including investigations of potential violations thereof, iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Insight Guru, its users, yourself or the public.

## 2\. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of our Site pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Site user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter certain identifying information, should we in the future require such information, to gain access to certain parts of the Site.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our Site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Site and your web experience.

To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles: 

  * Notice
  * Choice
  * Security
  * Access/Accuracy

## 3\. Notice

We do not currently provide your Personal Information to third parties, other than for any use or uses to which you give your consent.

We may also choose to make certain offers or services available to our users from third parties. If we do, during the registration process and at certain points thereafter in connection with specific offers we may ask you whether your Personal Information may be sent to third parties who have products, services and opportunities which may be useful to you. If you give your permission to allow third parties to contact you, your Personal Information (such as your contact information and other information collected during your visit to our Site) may be shared with data aggregators, marketers (possibly in the form of list rental), and other organizations. Insight Guru does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Insight Guru's behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Regardless of your decision regarding the sharing of your Personal Information, we may share broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information with our business partners. This aggregate information does not contain any Personal Information that can identify an individual user.

## 4\. Choice

You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Insight Guru. The notices we will provide where Insight Guru collects Personal Information on the Site should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.

## 5\. Security

We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the Personal Information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our employees and data processors that have access to, and are associated with the processing of your Personal Information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your information.

## 6\. Access / Accuracy

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Insight Guru wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. You may check your profile and add information, delete information or correct any incorrect information.

## 7\. Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

Our Site may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at our Site. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

## 8\. Links to Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

## 9\. Children's Privacy

The Site is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

## 10\. Commitment

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Insight Guru's Sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at help@trefis.com. _While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible._

## 11\. Your Consent

By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to Insight Guru's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

## 12\. Your California Privacy Rights

Insight Guru's Privacy Policy is to share Personal Information only with the owner's informed consent. With your consent, from time-to-time, Insight Guru may provide its business partners with contact details for direct marketing purposes of relevant services, products, and programs. If you no longer wish your information to be shared, please let us know. If you have further inquires regarding Insight Guru's Information Sharing Practices, please let us know.

The designated contact for these queries is help@trefis.com
